[{"question": "\u0427\u0442\u043e \u0442\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0435 Python?", "options": ["\u042f\u0437\u044b\u043a \u043f\u0440\u043e\u0433\u0440\u0430\u043c\u043c\u0438\u0440\u043e\u0432\u0430\u043d\u0438\u044f", "\u0422\u0438\u043f \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445", "\u041c\u0443\u0437\u044b\u043a\u0430\u043b\u044c\u043d\u044b\u0439 \u0438\u043d\u0441\u0442\u0440\u0443\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0442", "\u0417\u043c\u0435\u044f \u043d\u0430 \u0430\u043d\u0433\u043b\u0438\u0439\u0441\u043a\u043e\u043c"], "correct_option": 0}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u0442\u0438\u043f \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0438\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0446\u0435\u043b\u044b\u0445 \u0447\u0438\u0441\u0435\u043b?", "options": ["int", "float", "str", "natural"], "correct_option": 0}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u0442\u0438\u043f \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0438\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0434\u0440\u043e\u0431\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0447\u0438\u0441\u0435\u043b?", "options": ["int", "float", "str", "natural"], "correct_option": 1}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u0442\u0438\u043f \u0434\u0430\u043d\u043d\u044b\u0445 \u0438\u0441\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u043a?", "options": ["int", "float", "str", "natural"], "correct_option": 2}, {"question": "\u0427\u0442\u043e \u0445\u0440\u0430\u043d\u0438\u0442 \u0432 \u0441\u0435\u0431\u0435 \u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u043c\u0435\u043d\u043d\u0430\u044f?", "options": ["\u0418\u043c\u044f", "\u0422\u0438\u043f", "\u0417\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435", "\u0414\u043b\u0438\u043d\u0443 \u0438\u043c\u0435\u043d\u0438"], "correct_option": 2}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u0430\u044f \u0438\u0437 \u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u0443\u044e\u0449\u0438\u0445 \u0444\u0443\u043d\u043a\u0446\u0438\u044f \u043f\u0435\u0440\u0435\u043e\u0431\u0440\u0430\u0437\u0443\u0435\u0442 \u0434\u0435\u0441\u044f\u0447\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e\u0435 \u0447\u0438\u0441\u043b\u043e \u0432 \u0434\u0432\u043e\u0438\u0447\u043d\u043e\u0435?", "options": ["hex", "bin", "oct", "int"], "correct_option": 1}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u0430\u044f \u0438\u0437 \u0441\u043b\u0435\u0434\u0443\u044e\u0449\u0438\u0445 \u0444\u0443\u043d\u043a\u0446\u0438\u044f \u0432\u043e\u0437\u0432\u0440\u0430\u0449\u0430\u0435\u0442 \u0434\u043b\u0438\u043d\u0443 \u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u043a\u0438?", "options": ["count", "add", "bool", "len"], "correct_option": 3}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a\u043e\u0439 \u043c\u043e\u0434\u0443\u043b\u044c \u0432 Python \u0438\u043f\u043e\u043b\u044c\u0437\u0443\u0435\u0442\u0441\u044f \u0434\u043b\u044f \u0443\u043f\u0440\u0430\u0432\u0435\u043d\u0438\u044f \u0430\u0441\u0438\u043d\u0445\u0440\u043e\u043d\u043d\u044b\u043c\u0438 \u0444\u0443\u043d\u043a\u0446\u0438\u044f\u043c\u0438?", "options": ["asyncio", "logging", "aiogram", "aiosqlite"], "correct_option": 0}, {"question": "\u041a\u0430\u043a \u0441\u043e\u0437\u0434\u0430\u0442\u044c \u043f\u0443\u0441\u0442\u043e\u0439 \u0441\u043f\u0438\u0441\u043e\u043a \u0432 Python?", "options": ["0", "()", "[]", "{}"], "correct_option": 2}, {"question": "\u0427\u0442\u043e \u0434\u0435\u043b\u0430\u0435\u0442 \u0432\u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u0435\u043d\u043d\u0430\u044f \u0444\u0443\u043d\u043a\u0446\u0438\u044f input()?", "options": ["\u0421\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442 \u0446\u0435\u043b\u043e\u0435 \u0447\u0438\u0441\u043b\u043e \u0441 \u043a\u043b\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0430\u0442\u0443\u0440\u044b", "\u0421\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442 \u0441\u0442\u0440\u043e\u043a\u0443 \u0441 \u043a\u043b\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0430\u0442\u0443\u0440\u044b", "\u0421\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442 \u0434\u0440\u043e\u0431\u043d\u043e\u0435 \u0447\u0438\u0441\u043b\u043e \u0441 \u043a\u043b\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0430\u0442\u0443\u0440\u044b", "\u0421\u0447\u0438\u0442\u044b\u0432\u0430\u0435\u0442 boolean \u0437\u043d\u0430\u0447\u0435\u043d\u0438\u0435 \u0441 \u043a\u043b\u0430\u0432\u0438\u0430\u0442\u0443\u0440\u044b"], "correct_option": 1}]